Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.4.3
  - Subject files: European Skyways, 1926; 12 (Box 1572)
    - [Lowell Thomas and Guntav Lindenthal standing outside of a European Skyways plane], 1
    - Note [Mr. and Mrs. LT at (?) in Berlin with Guntav Lindenthal (?), famous patriarch and builder of the Hellgate Bridge, and Otto Merkle (?), founder of (?) (too small to read!!!), 2
    - [Two men with monkeys], 3
    - [First World Flight aircraft], 4
    - [First World Flight aircraft], 5
    - [Three pilots, one holding a raccoon], 6
    - [Three pilots, one with raccoon on chain], 7
    - [Man sitting in the cockpit of a First World Flight plane], 8
    - [First World Flight aircraft], 9
    - [aircraft], 10
    - [First World Flight aircraft], 11
    - [Pilot holding a raccoon with two other pilots], 12
    - [First World Flight aircraft], 13
    - [First World Flight aircraft in the water], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas standing in front of a plane and automobile], 15
    - [River and a windmill], 16
    - Note [Falls Unbestellbar Zuruck An KODAK Gens. M. b. H., Berlin SW 68 Markgrafenstrasse 76, Abteilung Fur Fachphotographen], 17
    - [People by an aircraft], 18
    - Note: 1926 Flying in Europe negs. [negatives], 19
    - Note: European Skyways 1926, 20
  - Subject files: European Skyways, 1926; 13 (Box 1572)
    - [European Skyways aircraft], 1
    - [Aerial view of snowy mountains], 2
    - [Aerial view of a city in Europe], 3
    - [Aerial view of snowy mountains], 4
    - [European Skyways planes over fields], 5
    - [European Skywways aircraft over a castle], 6
    - [European Skyways plane flying over snowy mountains], 7
    - [Aerial view of mountains], 8
    - [Aerial view of snowy mountains], 9
    - [European Skyways plane flying over a forest], 10
    - [European Skyways plane flying over a European city], 11
    - [European Skyways plane over fields in Europe], 12
    - [European skyways plane in the clouds], 13
    - [European Skyways plane over European fields], 14
    - [European Skyways plane flying over farmlands], 15
    - [European Skyways plane soraing over clouds], 16
    - [European Skyways plane flying in the clouds], 17
    - [European Skyways plane flying over a European city], 18
    - [European Skyways plane flying over European city], 19
    - [European Skyways plane over mountains], 20
    - [European Skyways plane in the sky], 21
    - [Two European Skyways planes over a European city], 22
    - [European Skyways plane over a city in Europe], 23
    - [European Skyways plane flying over a city in Europe], 24
    - [European Skyways plane flying over a European city], 25
    - [European Skyways plane flying over snowy mountains], 26
    - Note: [outside of negative envelope] Negs. of pictures in European Skyways, 27
    - Note: [inside of negative envelope], 28
  - Subject files: European Skyways, 1926; 14 (Box 1572)
    - [European Skyways plane over a town in Europe], 1
    - [European Skyways plane over a city in Europe], 2
    - [European Skyways plane flying over a European city], 3
    - [European Skyways plane flying over European city], 4
    - [European Skyways planes over a city in Europe], 5
    - [European Skyways plane over a city in Europe], 6
    - [European Skyways plane flying over a city in Europe], 7
    - [European Skyways plane over a city in Europe], 8
    - [European Skyways plane flying by a European city], 9
    - [European Skyways plane flying over a castle in Europe], 10
    - [European Skyways plane flying over a European city], 11
    - [Sail boat in icy water], 12
    - [European Skyways plane over a city in Europe], 13
  - Subject files: European Skyways, 1926; 15 (Box 1572)
    - [European Skyways plane flying over a canal in Europe], 1
    - [European Skyways plane over mountains in Europe], 2
    - [European Skyways plane over Europe], 3
    - [European Skyways over a European city], 4
    - [European Skyways plane over a city in Europe], 5
    - [European Skyways plane over a city in Europe], 6
    - [Aerial view of mountains-European Skyways], 7
    - [Aerial view of a European landscape-European Skyways], 8
    - [Aerial view of snowy mountains-European Skyways], 9
    - [Arial view of mountains-European Skyways], 10
    - [Aerial view of mountains from a European Skyways plane], 11
    - [Aerial view of fields from a European Skyways plane], 12
    - [Aerial view of a European city-European Skyways], 13
    - [European town-European Skyways], 14
    - [Aerial view of a European city-European Skyways], 15
    - [Mountains-European Skyways], 16
    - [Mountains-European Skyways], 17
  Box 1573
- Subject Files, 2.1.4.3
  - Subject files: European Skyways, 1926; 1 (Box 1573)
    - [Aerial view of mountains-European Skyways], 1
    - [View of a harbor from a European Skyways plane], 2
    - [Aerial view of a European harbor-European Skyways ], 3
    - [View from a European Skyways plane], 4
    - [Aerial view of a river from a European Skyways plane], 5
    - [Pisa, Italy-European Skyways], 6
    - [A twister (?)-European Skyways], 7
    - [European river-European Skyways], 8
    - [Aerial view of a European city-European Skyways], 9
    - [A twister (?) European Skyways], 10
    - [Aerial view of a smoking volcano taken from a European Skyways plane], 11
    - [European city-European Skyways], 12
    - [Aerial view of a smoking volcano-European Skyways], 13
    - [Aerial view of a city-European Skyways], 14
    - [View of a European city from a European Skyways plane], 15
    - [Mountain range-European Skyways], 16
    - [European city-European Skyways], 17
    - [European city-European Skyways], 18
    - [Aerial view of a European city-European Skyways], 19
    - [Aerial view of the pyramids in Egypt-European Skyways], 20
    - [European town by the water-European Skyways], 21
    - [People on boats in front of a city-European Skyways], 22
    - [Aerial view of mountains-European Skyways], 23
    - [European town-European Skyways], 24
    - [Fields in Europe-European Skyways], 25
    - [City in Europe-European Skyways], 26
    - [European city-European Skyways], 27
    - [European Skyways plane over a city in Europe], 28
    - [European Skyways plane flying over Europe], 29
  - Subject files: European Skyways, 1926; 2 (Box 1573)
    - [Two European Skyways planes over a European city], 1
    - [European Skyways plane over a city in Europe], 2
    - [European Skyways plane over a city in Europe], 3
    - [European Skyways plane over a city in Europe], 4
    - [European Skyways plane flying over a city in Europe], 5
    - [European Skyways plane over a European city], 6
    - [European Skyways plane over a river in Europe], 7
    - [European Skyways plane over a city in Europe], 8
    - [European Skyways plane flying over a city in Europe], 9
    - [European Skyways plane over fields in Europe], 10
    - [European Skyways plane flying over a castle in Europe], 11
    - [Two European Skyways planes flying over Europe], 12
    - [View of a tower from a European Skyways plane, 13
    - [European Skyways plane flying over a sail boat], 14
    - [European Skyways plane flying over a city in Russia (?)], 15
  - Subject files: Example of popularity, undated; 3 (Box 1573)
    - [Cross streets of "Lowell" and "Thomas"], 1
    - [Bathroom that Lowell Thomas used. Sign: "Lowell Thomas used this shower. June 1, 1934], 2
    - [Church that Lowell Thomas went to?], 3
    - [Church that Lowell Thomas went to? Got married in?], 4
    - Note [LT on Cinerama float in Pasadena Rose Parade-40,000 orchids on the float.], 5
  - Subject files: The Explorers Club, undated; 4 (Box 1573)
    - [The Explorers Club-Room with stuffed animals], 1
    - [The Explorers Club-meeting room (?)], 2
    - [Members of the Explorers Club sitting at a banquet table], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and others outside of the Lowell Thomas Building-The Explorers Club], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and another man speaking at a Explorers Club event], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with other Explorers Club members], 6
    - [A large ship], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas, Lowell Thomas Jr. and other members of the Explorers Club], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas, Lowell Thomas Jr. and other members of the Explorers Club], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas and other members of the Explorers Club in front of a banner reading, "Most of Outer Space"], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas signing his name into pavement], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas with other members of the Explorers Club standing outside of an airplane], 12
  - Subject files: Family, circa 1920s; 5 (Box 1573)
    - [Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, and son with two other young men], 1
    - [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas with Lowell Thomas Jr. (?)], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, and their son, Lowell Thomas Jr.], 3
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas playing with Lowell Thomas Jr.], 4
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas kneeling next to Lowell Thomas Jr.], 5
    - [Man turned away from the camera], 6
    - [Mr. and Mrs. Lowell Thomas with their son, Lowell Thomas Jr.], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. at the beach], 8
    - [Building on fire at the end of a boardwalk], 9
    - [Man and woman driving in an automobile], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. riding on a scooter], 11
    - [Man and woman surrounded by a crowd of people], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas walking on the beach with a large group of people], 13
    - [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. playing in the sand], 14
    - [People pushing a plane out into the ocean], 15
    - [Building burning by the boardwalk], 16
    - [People watching a building burn by the boardwalk], 17
    - [Mr. and Mrs. Lowell Thomas standing in front of a man in an automobile], 18
    - [Burning building by the boardwalk], 19
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr.], 20
    - [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas holding Lowell Thomas Jr.'s hand], 21
    - [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas sitting next to Lowell Thomas Jr.], 22
    - [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas wearing a fur coat], 23
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas holding Lowell Thomas Jr.], 24
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. on a blanket outside], 25
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. outside on a blanket], 26
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. on a blanket outside], 27
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas (?), Lowell Thomas Jr., and another girl outside], 28
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. sitting in the grass], 29
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. on the lawn], 30
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas (?), Lowell Thomas Jr., and a young girl], 31
  - Subject files: Family, circa 1920s; 6 (Box 1573)
    - [A baby getting a bath], 1
    - [Baby in a bath], 2
    - [Baby getting a bath], 3
    - [Baby getting out of the bath], 4
    - [Baby getting dried off], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. and Frances Ryan Thomas], 6
    - [Fracnes Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. on a bench], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. climbing on a bench], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas, Lowell Thomas Jr., and Frances Ryan Thomas], 9
    - [Fracnes Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. playing on the beach, 10
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. on a bench by the sea], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas holding Lowell Thomas Jr. at the beach], 12
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. at the beach], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. on a bench at the beach], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas with Lowell Thomas Jr. at the beach], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. playing in the grass], 16
    - [Fracnes Ryan Thomas holding an umbrella over Lowell Thomas Jr.], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas and his family at the beach], 18
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. at the beach], 19
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas and a young man (Lowell Thomas Jr.) standing in front of an automobile], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. and Frances Ryan Thomas at the beach], 21
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr.], 22
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. playing with blocks], 23
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. sitting in the sand], 24
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr.], 25
    - [Man sitting at the beach (relative of Lowell Thomas?)], 26
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. sitting on a man's lap at the beach], 27
    - [Woman standing with Lowell Thomas Jr. and another little boy], 28
    - [Woman with Lowell Thomas Jr. and another little boy at the park], 29
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. sitting with another little boy], 30
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. kissing a young boy on the cheek], 31
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. sitting in a cart and a young girl (Lowell Thomas' Daughter?)], 32
    - [A young girl riding a tricycle and Lowell Thomas Jr. sitting in a cart], 33
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. and a young girl], 34
    - [A young girl standing behind Lowell Thomas Jr.], 35
  - Subject files: Family, circa 1920s - 1930s; 7 (Box 1573)
    - Note: John, Early Cloverbrook negatives, L.T. + Mrs. L.T. + L.T. Jn., file for vault, 1
    - Sonny in Indian costume, 2
    - Sonny and boy on porch of Clover Brook, 3
    - Sonny, with dogs, in uniform standing on lawn, 4
    - Sonny at Glenness, with skates, age 11, 5
    - Sonny in uniform, atanding on front porch steps at Clover Brook, 6
    - Sonny in uniform, close-up, waist, 7
    - Sonny skiing, 8
    - Taft baseball team [Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 9
    - Taft baseball team [Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 10
    - Taft baseball team [Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 11
    - Sonny and friend on lawn under tent, 12
    - Mrs. L.T. in garden, 13
    - Mrs. L.T. in garden, 14
    - Mrs. L.T. in garden, 15
    - Mrs. L.T. and dog in garden, also some tulips showing, 16
    - Mrs. L.T. and dog in garden, also some tulips showing, 17
    - Mrs. L.T. with three dogs stitting on front porch at Clover Brook, 18
    - Mrs. L.T. views showing Mrs. L.T. with cat and dog on lawn at Clover Brook farm, near road, house in background, 19
    - Mrs. L.T. views showing Mrs. L.T. with cat and dog on lawn at Clover Brook farm, near road, house in background, 20
    - Mrs. L.T. views showing Mrs. L.T. with cat and dog on lawn at Clover Brook farm, near road, house in background, 21
    - Mrs. L.T. views showing Mrs. L.T. with cat and dog on lawn at Clover Brook farm, near road, house in background, 22
    - Mrs. L.T. and grey culbertson with big dog, 23
    - Mrs. L.T. on porch holding dogs, 24
    - Mrs. L.T. and dog, 25
    - Mrs. L.T. and dog, 26
    - Mrs. L.T. riding, 27
    - L.T. riding at Clover Brook Farm, 28
    - L.T. on horse, 29
    - L.T. with chefs hat on at barbecue grounds at Clover Brook Farm, 30
    - L.T. with chefs hat on at barbecue grounds at Clover Brook Farm, 31
    - L.T. and Jimmy Wallington, taken in the studio, 32
    - L.T. and Jimmy Wallington, taken in the studio, 33
    - L.T. on "Pinto", 34
    - L.T. and big dog "Bouncer", 35
    - L.T. and Miss Moore, 36
    - L.T., Mrs. L.T. and L.T., Jr., 37
    - Portrait of Mrs. L.T. and L.T., Jr., 38
    - Portrait of L.T., Mrs. L.T. and L.T., Jr., 39
    - Portrait of L.T., Mrs. L.T. and L.T., Jr., 40
  Box 1574
- Subject Files, 2.1.4.3
  - Subject files: Family, circa 1920s - 1930s; 1 (Box 1574)
    - Family; [Town on the shore], 1
    - Family; L.T. at 9 months old [likely actually L.T., Jr.], 2
    - Family; Pherbia Thomas Thornburg, circa 1930s, 3
    - Family; Harry G. Thomas, circa 1940s, 4
    - Family; Lowell + Frances Thomas in costumes, circa 1960s, 5
    - Family; Lowell + Frances Thomas; Thomas E. Dewey, 6
    - Family; Sonny, close-up, circa 1936, 7
    - Family; Sonny, close-up, circa 1936, 8
    - Family; Sonny with cat, 9
    - Family; [Sonny on a horse], 10
    - Family; [Sonny with a dog], 11
    - Family; [Sonny (?) on skis], 12
    - Family; [Sonny standing on a railing], 13
    - Family; [Sonny on skis], 14
    - Family; [Sonny on a walkway], 15
    - Family; [Sonny next to a baby cow], 16
    - Family; [Sonny putting wood in a wagon], 17
    - Family; [Sonny sitting in the grass], 18
    - Family; [Sonny holding a baby chick], 19
    - Family; [First two photos-Sonny and his dog. Second two photos-A large house], 20
    - Family; [Sonny and his dog], 21
    - Family; [LT, Lt Jr. and two other men holding skis], 22
    - Family; [Man wearing a hat], 23
    - Family; [Man with gun standing next to a horse], 24
    - Family; [Man sitting with two children on a hill], 25
    - Family; [Frances Ryan Thomas lounging outside], 26
    - Family; [Lowell Thomas and a man with skis], 27
    - Family; [Lowell Thomas and a man on skis], 28
    - Family; [Two men on a porch], 29
    - Family; [Two men on a porch], 30
    - Family; [A man and a young boy climbing over a fence], 31
    - Family; [Man and young boy sitting on a fence], 32
    - Family; [Mans showing a young boy his gun], 33
    - Family; [Sonny (?) Lowell Thomas Jr (?)], 34
    - Family; [Lowell Thomas and his family sitting on a porch], 35
    - Family; [People sitting on the porch], 36
    - Family; [Lowell Thomas and his family standing on a porch], 37
    - Family; [Woman, man, and boy on a sled], 38
    - Family; [Woman and her dog on a lawn], 39
    - Family; [Portrait of Lowell Thomas as a boy], 40
  - Subject files: Family, circa 1920s - 1930s; 2 (Box 1574)
    - [Sonny (?) playing in the grass], 1
    - [A baby sitting in a bowl in the lawn], 2
    - [Sonny (?) putting logs in a wagon], 3
    - [Young boy sitting next to a fence], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. (?) on steps], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. outside], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. riding a tricycle on a porch], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. standing on skis], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. on skis], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. (?) painting a bench], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. painting a bench], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. outside with a dog], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. on skis], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. on skis], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. and a dog], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. and a horse], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. and a horse], 17
    - [Man and Sonny (?) on ice skates], 18
    - [Sonny at Glenness with ice skates], 19
    - [Boy playing the clarinet on a rock wall], 20
    - [Man diving into a lake], 21
    - [Man diving into a lake], 22
    - [Sonny (?) in uniform], 23
    - [Boy jumping off a diving board], 24
    - [Sonny (?) driving a tractor], 25
    - [Sonny (?) riding a tractor], 26
    - [Little boy (Lowell Thomas Jr? Sonnny?) walking through snowy branches], 27
    - [Little boy playing with his dog on the lawn], 28
    - [Little boy standing on a rock in the middle of a stream], 29
    - [Little boy sitting with tulips], 30
    - [Little boy pushing a wheelbarrow], 31
    - [Man and Sonny? Lowell Thomas Jr.?], 32
  - Subject files: Family, undated; 3 (Box 1574)
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) with his military group], 1
    - [Family portrait], 2
    - [Family portrait], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) in a hospital], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas' family (?)], 5
    - [Man with a moustache wearing a bowler hat], 6
  - Subject files: Family: Christmas (Lowell and Mrs. Marianna Munn Thomas), circa 1979; 4 (Box 1574)
    - [Lowell Thomas with Mrs. Marianna Munn Thomas and a man at Chirstmas], 1
  - Subject files: Family: Early family, undated; 5 (Box 1574)
    - [Man in a suit], 1
    - [Letter with two photos of a man in a suit], 2
    - [Man in a suit], 3
    - [Photos of a man in a suit with his wife], 4
    - [Man sitting at a desk], 5
    - [Man writing at a desk, 6
    - [Drawing of two little girls], 7
    - Note: Dear Ray(Mr. R. H. Coulter): I have blown up your transparencies, and am now returning them to you with a set of the pictures. I wish you would send them along to Rollo Jackson's children. How many remain if his family. I would appreciate it if you could give me their names and addresses. Again many many thanks for doing all this for me. Cordially, Lowell Thomas [unsigned], 8
  - Subject files: Family: Early family, undated; 6 (Box 1574)
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. with their dog], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. petting a dog], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. with his dogs], 3
    - [Softball team], 4
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas, Lowell Thomas Jr., and a man holding a cat], 5
    - [Man and woman holding their dogs], 6
    - [Tracks in the snow leading to a house (Clover Brook?)], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas talking to a man in an automobile], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr.], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas], 10
    - [Portrait of a man], 11
    - [Portrait of a woman], 12
    - [Portrait of a woman], 13
    - Note [Mr. A.C. McCorkel father of Eunice Ryan and grandfather of Mrs. Lowell Thomas.], 14
    - Note [Mrs. A.C. McCorkel mother of Eunice Ryan and grandmother of Mrs. Lowell Thomas. Superior, Nebraska.], 15
    - Note [Family. Mrs. Eunice Ryan grandfather- Mrs. LT], 16
    - Note [LT and Mrs. T LT mother. Mrs. T mother Mrs. Ryan (?)], 17
    - Note [The Picture of Eunice McCortrel now Mrs. H. P. Ryan The Mother-in-law of Lowell Thomas, The commentator and world traveler. W.R. Loar Artistic Photographer and dealer in picture frames, albums, matts, etc. Superior, Nebraska 1887], 18
  - Subject files: Family: Frances Ryan Thomas, circa 1960s; 7 (Box 1574)
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas's family], 1
    - [Dog and woman sitting in a chair], 2
    - [Man holding a child and a painting over the fireplace], 3
    - [Fracnes Ryan's family], 4
    - [Two people on skis], 5
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas's family], 6
    - [Painting of Lowell Thomas on skis], 7
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas (mother?)], 8
    - [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas], 9
    - [Mrs. Fracnes Ryan Thomas holding a pot], 10
    - [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas holding a pot outside], 11
    - [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas outside holding a pot], 12
    - [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas holding a pot], 13
    - [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas sitting outside, holding a pot], 14
    - [Mrs. Fracnes Ryan Thomas holding a pot on the stairs], 15
    - [Mrs. Frances Ryan holding a pot outside], 16
  - Subject files: Family: Frances Ryan Thomas, undated; 8 (Box 1574)
    - [Portrait of a young girl], 1
    - [Three men and two women standing outside-Francis Ryan's Family], 2
    - [Portrait of Fracnes Ryan (?) as a young woman], 3
    - [Woman holding a baby], 4
    - [Woman holding a baby], 5
    - [Women holding a baby], 6
    - [Women holding a baby outside], 7
    - [Two women sitting on steps with a baby], 8
    - [Two women sitting outside with a baby], 9
    - [Two women with a baby outside], 10
    - [Members of Frances Ryan's family], 11
    - [Relatives of Frances Ryan Thomas], 12
  - Subject files: Family: Frances Ryan Thomas, undated; 9 (Box 1574)
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas and her family members], 1
    - [Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas (mother?)], 2
    - [Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas (mother?)], 3
    - [Portrait of a little girl], 4
    - [Woman in a sunhat], 5
    - [Woman with a hat], 6
  - Subject files: Family: Frances Ryan Thomas (Ohio), undated; 10 (Box 1574)
    - [Church in Ohio (?)], 1
    - [Girl sitting on a fence], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas standing outside a house], 3
    - [Frances Ryan's home in Ohio (?)], 4
    - [Church in Ohio (?)], 5
    - [Frances Ryan's house in Ohio (?)], 6
    - [House], 7
    - [Fracnes Ryan Thomas (?) standing on the steps outside her home (?)], 8
    - [People standing outside of a house], 9
    - [A country lane in Ohio], 10
    - [Automobile on a dirt road in Ohio (?)], 11
    - [Church (?) in Ohio], 12
    - [Fracnes Ryan looking at flowers], 13
    - [Frances Ryan standing on steps], 14
    - [people standing outside a house in Ohio (?)], 15
  - Subject files: Family: Frances Ryan Thomas (found in Frances's personal papers), undated; 11 (Box 1574)
    - [Frances Ryan's relatives], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and others sitting on a porch], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. and a woman], 3
    - [Fracnes Ryan Thomas (?) standing beneath a palm tree], 4
    - [Man in a hat standing outside], 5
    - [Woman laying on a blanket outside], 6
    - Frances Ryan (?) standing next to a building], 7
    - [Women and a small child in front ofa building], 8
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas (?) standing in a dirt road], 9